The Knights' tactics
are clearly working.
The Eagles haven't
scored a single point
in the first half.
Could they be pulling
off the miracle today?
They're a bunch of
third-rate players
with bargain-
bin salaries.
Why the fuck are they
good all of a sudden?
You fucking idiot.
I thought you said this
would be no problem.
What the fuck am I
paying you for?
It's gotta be a fluke.
It's gotta be Ted.
He was my assistant.
He knows all
my fucking plays.
But what are you
gonna do about it?
I have...
I have a plan
to turn this around.
Trust me.
You better not
be bullshitting me.
I swear to God
that if I can't
lead this team
to victory, I...
I'll resign.
This is your
last chance, son.
Last chance!
Am I clear?
Don't fuck it up.
Shit.
Looks like
I've got no choice.
Kent!
What's up, coach?
That broke-ass
team's only got
one star player.
Quarterback.
Take him out.
They can't
win this game.
You bet.
Going on!